Well, GitHub and Verscell are not the
only places that you can deploy your
code. Another option is Netifi. Um, and
they also have a free account. So, what
I'm going to do is I'm going to click
sign up.
And then it's going to say, what do you
want to sign up with? I'm going to sign
up with my GitHub. And then I'm going to
continue. And then it says just like for
sale, it's asking if Netifi can access
my GitHub account. And the main thing it
wants to access is my email address. I'm
going to authorize that.
And now um it's asking for my first
name.
And then how am I planning to use
Netifi? I'm going to use it for personal
things. Um I like web apps.
We're going to go with other here. What
is the name of my team?
And then we'll continue to deploy. So
now there's a couple ways to do this.
Um, the easiest way for us is to choose
GitHub.
And it says, "Please authorize it."
We're going to authorize Netlefi to
access some of our resources on our
account. Um, and we're going to let it
know specifically which resources we
want it to use, and it is going to
verify that we are who we say we are
using our email address. So, let's
authorize that similar thing that we
authorize for sale for. We'll hit
continue. And once again, you now have a
choice. You can give it access to all of
your repositories or only specific ones.
I'm going to go with only specific ones.
And I'm going to click on dice roller.
And I'm going to click install.
And here it is. Um,
and it says deploy dice roller to
Netlefi. And I'm going to click, I don't
know if you saw that, edit uh deployment
settings. And instead of deploying from
main, I'm going to click deploy. If you
merged all of your code from main um
from your branch into main, then you can
just go ahead and deploy main. And that
is the only thing I'm going to change.
And I'm going to click deploy dice
roller to netify. And now it's going to
take a little bit. And it does offer you
to play a game. It is a matching game.
You can play a matching game while you
wait. Wow. What are the chances that I
would get a first try? Anyway, I'm going
to return to deploy because um this one
is complete and it's working on it's
complete the initialization. It's
completed building, deploying, and
cleaning up. And it's deployed it. Um so
now we can open production deploy. Here
it is. And our dice are ready to roll.
We can go ahead and freeze them. And
awesome. So let's come back over to
Netifi. Um,
and you can see here is the perma link.
And if you open it up, you can see in
the top URL bar it's https,
a whole bunch of stuff.netifi.app.
And your app is now publicly accessible
to the world. Anyone you give this link
to will be able to use your app. And
that is how you'd play on Netifi.